Okay okay ladies
let's start shall we so welcome thank you for coming to our to our training today
it's nice to see a couple of new faces and some old faces that we now in love
um hopefully we can all get something out of today's call um I know that some people
are doing some dom stuff on cam already so please let us know if you've got your
own tips or your we mentioned um
on here so we'll go for it and Laura I just love that picture of me and you from
the shoot Georgia put that on there and I was like oh love that pic it's so nice
it's amazing I think every single photo on this Zoom is from the shoot right because
you put some more on did you yeah yeah every single one of the pictures amazing
so so amazing it was such a good shoot I would definitely I think we'll book that
um again at some point maybe when you're back do one day yes please I'd
love to okay let's go for it okay
do you want to do this first bit jay should we take it yeah sure okay so what
is the dominatrix I actually took the um definition of google and then I wrote out
well from the oxford dictionary and then I wrote out um what my definition was um
so a dominatrix aka dom is a woman who takes the dominating role in BDSM
activities she usually goes by mistress and or goddess a
good dom has his best interests at heart and is confident and professional she knows
her worth and trusts her judgment she connects to her subs forms relationships with
them and she understands it's more about the connection rather than just barking
orders she is intuitive to a sub's needs and desires so
what is a submissive and once again I took the definition of oxford dictionary and
then wrote mine out and so they said a submissive is a person who takes their submissive
role in BDSM activities they are ready to conform to their mistress and please
here they are obedient loyal and attentive they enjoy the power play of giving
up all control to their mistress and they want to be held in a safe space to explore
their fantasies another
lovely picture of Tristan being a prop there I think you're here aren't you k somewhere
amazing picture of you okay so we'll talk about some of the types
of subs then before we go ahead so some of the types of submissives that you might
come across on webcam so loyal subs amazing of
course we all these are the ones we all want subs that will come back time and time
again that will build a good relationship with you and earn you lots of money on
webcam this is I think this is your
domain more than mine isn't it uh Georgia do you work a lot okay yeah sure so
just touching on the loyal subs again I feel like if you find a sub that you've got
a good connection with and they're really happy with what you're delivering to them
then they're going to be loyal because for them also it's hard to find
like a really um like a mistress who actually knows what she's doing because a lot
of people say you know oh I do domination but then they don't really know what it
means truly so hopefully you'll all know even a little bit more what it means after
today and yeah if they find you and they're like really happy with you they will
stay because I've still got guys and honestly this is no words of a lie I've still
got clients who have been there for nine years and they've been coming back and coming
back and even if I take time off cam I go back online and the first day it's like
they're all there and I'm like you must just sit on this every day used to be just
be there when I come back on um so yeah I've got so many loyal subs over the years
so it's it's great um okay so sissies this is um
like the the clients who would like to dress up um as a woman usually they'll
be you know they can just go get their own um so like sometimes they'll come on cam
and they'll be more dolled up than you will they'll have the wig the hair like makeup,
the outfit and they like to be called a little slut and a whore and stuff like
that and they also like the fantasy of being pimped out for you, for their mistress
to be able to make some more money for you to give to you so you can pimp
them out with guys or girls, it's most likely to be guys.
So yeah this one's very interesting and it's just something to play with really.
We actually have, we're just going to touch on each thing on this call, I mean we'll
go into a bit of detail but on the website we have a domination course and in there
there's a whole section on sissification and it gives you things you can say, things
you can do with these types of subs. So if you want to look into this further please
go to the website after this and you can take pictures or write down you know all
the different phrases you can say to each different type of sub.
Okay, next one please. So next we have cook holds.
Okay so cook holds is basically they want to
watch you or fantasise about you with other guys or just other people actually, it
doesn't just have to be guys. You do get quite a lot like that and
even with the subs they say sometimes you know if you even if you've got a boyfriend
I would like to save both of you or you know make both your lives easier and stuff
like that. So yeah the subs they know usually that
your relationship with them is never going to be a sexual one so they like the idea
of you doing that with somebody else and telling them all about it.
This is a good one but couples if you've got a couples profile as well you know anyone
who has a singles profile can also have a couples profile either with another friend,
a girl or with a guy. So I've got a profile with my boyfriend and we get loads of
cook holds that's probably the most the thing we most get which is guys that just
want to talk through a fantasy of being made to sit in a corner basically and
told you know this is that they're pathetic to be humiliated a little bit
to be you know told like this is how this is how a real man does it like to be compared
and some of them have sometimes have like in their fantasy they like forced by
so they like to be told how you're going to force them to do things with the man.
Of course you talk through this and we'll talk a bit more about boundaries and you
know getting to know what your client wants but this is all coming from them this
is all what they like a part of their fantasy is often like forced by and clean up
stuff like that so not actually getting involved in the sex but just being used as
part of the activity. Okay hello you've got your hand up you
might need to unmute yourself if you want to say hey it's just actually written in
the volume turned up okay on your laptop make
sure the volume's turned up on your laptop otherwise maybe come out of the meeting
and back in if it's not working first time.
Yeah and then when it says about joining with video and audio just press accept and
I should be okay. Okay so that's cuckolds um you
want to do that one yeah sure so slave slash slave trainer so um
so basically with the slave trainer and it's like you're training them up to
be the perfect sub for you for their mistress and it could be like
so many different things you could do with them um but what I like to do if I have
like a full-time slave like you know someone who's coming back all the time and they're
going away and doing things for me they're reporting back and I always like them
to check in with me so and also I always like to make
them do something that is going to better their lives so of course you're going to
have them do tasks for you for like for their mistress they're going to do stuff
that's going to please you but I also like them to do stuff that's going to um like
to improve an area of their life so if I've got a full-time like arrangement going
on and you know they're always coming back to me I ask them what's an area of your
life that you would like to improve and I actually got this tip from Michelle um
she's on a Zoom last year with us and a dominatrix she's amazing we will we will
get it back um and what was I just gonna say sorry I've lost
all trailer thoughts oh yeah um I asked them what area of your life would you like
to improve and a lot of the time they say you know oh I would like to be in better
shape or you know be healthier or lose weight or something like that um and I I tell
them okay because you know I want you to be like I don't want to look at you like
that I want you to be in a better shape for your mistress and you know you always
bring it back to what you want but it's actually like they've told you they want
that you know so then you can say to them um I want you to check in with me every
weekend I want to see your weight dropping and your measurements drop and photos
and this and that so you're actually like helping them to like better their lives
so that can be a part of the slave training so it doesn't have to just be stuff like
you know I want you to be like a better sub and more obedient and you train them
to be more obedient you can also train them to just be better be a better person
or you know work on the part of their life that they've said that they would like
to and so yeah that's something a little bit different with slave training that I
never used to do but then when that this um other dominatrix told us about it and
she's a really successful dominatrix I was like oh yeah this is great because this
feels good to me as well to not just be like you know having them do all kinds
of crazy stuff to actually as well be doing something positive with them you know
and so yeah I think that's a nice one and with the slaves as well as
it's going to be more of a um like a close connection and relationship and you know
the coming back time and time again you can have them sign a contract so you can
either get one online or you can just make one yourself and have them like sign
a contract to basically say that they're devoted to you but you know however long
it's going to be or you know it doesn't have to be open-ended kind of thing um another
thing you can have them do you can have them write out the contract every day or
every week depending on how regularly you're speaking you can write it out every
single time like you know on paper and sign and date it and show you that they've
done it and so even when you're not on cam with them they're still doing things outside
of cam thinking of you ready for your next session and so yeah so when
you have a slave always set them tasks ready for the next the next session so then
like I said they're doing something while they're away and you're always on their
minds and stuff like that and it probably feels more valuable for them like you
know that you're not just in the session with them you're also outside of the session
with the things that you've asked them to do yes next one please well okay
so new versus experienced so I feel like
with the subs um a lot of the time you'll get new subs and they'll
just and I think the next point is gonna talk about this they'll say oh
you know I'll do this this and this and I'm into this I'm into this and like and
then you think oh great like I'm gonna have this really amazing full-time like sub
that's gonna be here all the time spending money and then it's like that's not usually
the case with the new ones I feel but then with the experience so they understand
how the relationship works and they understand that you know it's more like about
the connection with you just one dom rather than trying to like go and like
you know come with everyone and but yeah the more you do it the more you'll
pick out like which ones are new and which ones experienced and yeah you'll
see you'll see which um like who to spend your time with because that's one of the
last points here is time wasters and you'll get them coming and promising the world
some of them they'll be like yeah you know I'll pay all your bills and I'll and I'll
like clean your house and like blah blah blah like all this stuff and then you just
never see them again you're like hmm great got my hopes up for nothing um so yeah
you'll start to see like you know because I just kind of know in the first
few minutes now like if they're going to be a good one or not because usually if
they come in promise the whales then probably not so so yeah just bear that in mind
and switches I'll let you speak about this one well you probably know more about
that than me um yeah so switches actually a lot a lot of guys
that I end up in like sub dom thing with is often it's like a switch sort of arrangement
so yeah a switch is just somebody that is willing to switch from sub to dominant
so you know you can both take that role at any given time And there's lots of different
type of switches. I mean, I am a switch myself, cause I really enjoy being sub and
I really enjoy being Dom. So it really just depends on the relationship that you
have with the individual client, what that looks like.
I have had a really good sub that I really enjoyed, that's good to say working with,
I guess it is working with, isn't it? But recently, and it wasn't until I really
got to know him and we had a really good relationship and I started finding out about
why he got into being a sub and why he had this fantasy and then we got chatting
and then the relationship developed to a point where he could feel
a bit more confident within himself and start to experiment with being a Dom with
me. And that was just a really lovely progression of our relationship when we got
to this trusting stage that he could try something that I gave him permission to
try, you know? So I think, yeah, just being open, just being open
and being curious with your subs when they do show a different side, can encourage
them to switch if they want to and if you're comfortable with that as well.
Yeah, so I think that's it for that one, isn't it?
So, oh, nothing's coming in,
what's happening? Oh, there we go, so getting to
know yourself. So really important, the first thing that you need to do when you're
working with anybody is to get to know them, isn't it?
So you know how the sessions are gonna go, what the relationship's gonna be like,
what type of sub they are from that list that we've just seen.
So what are their wants and desires? So it's okay, I think this is a thing
that, you know, a lot of people slip up on or aren't so sure about, but it's okay
to ask questions. So it's okay to ask like loads of questions when you're first working
with somebody. You know, when you're first approached by a sub, like Georgia
says, there are lots of guys that will just come into your room and just expect you
to do certain things, you know? They'll just go throughout the girls on the cam and
just expect them to maybe bark orders or do this certain thing that they like, which
is fine. But if you're, you know, in a proper sub-dom relationship, then it's about
establishing boundaries and knowing how each other's gonna work and what
each other's gonna like beforehand. So it's okay not to jump straight into doing
activities or a session with somebody, but to ask loads of questions first.
So I think there's some ideas on this side as well about what sort of questions you
might ask. And staying open in order to listen.
So another thing that people do is think that, so one, think that they shouldn't
ask questions if they're dominant, which is not true, you should always ask questions.
And two, think that they should have everything worked out already, that they should
know everything because they're in control because you're the dom, you should already
know everything, which is not the case. You know, being curious and asking questions
about somebody to find out what they like also means that you have to stay open in
order to listen to what they like. So not thinking that you know without, you know,
without speaking to them, being curious about them.
So you can ask them what type of submission that they're into and do they have experience
with that and do they have experience with other things that you might like?
Again, like Gee said, we've got the whole course on domination.
So there's loads of, it will tell you about all the different types and it will give
you some examples for that. And like I was saying about my sub
recently, you know, I was chatting to him about what got him into submission and
he could tell me like the stories and it was a really nice way to kind of bond with
each other. And I got to know why, because I knew what got him into being submissive,
I also could gauge like how he wanted to feel.
So this is something that I try and gauge when I'm working in a dom way is how
does the client want me to make them feel?
Because some will come in with a particular fantasy where maybe they've been caught
doing something and they were humiliated and that's how they want to feel.
They want to be back in that place of feeling humiliated because they've done that
bad thing. Or others, it might be a totally different thing.
Like they just want to feel inferior. They want to feel like there's a goddess that
they're looking up to that will make them do anything so that they, all control is
out of their hands and they can just relax into your control.
So different submissives want to feel different ways.
So it's not just about you know, taking control and getting them to do stuff.
It's about thinking about how they want to feel and then doing what you can to make
them feel that with your words or with your actions.
What is their ideal Dom's relationship and what do they enjoy most about it?
So yeah, it's a good thing to ask or gauge when you're first talking to someone,
like what does your ideal, what is your ideal Dom like and what would your ideal
session look like? So you can be as blunt as that and just ask them what it looks
like for them and what they enjoy about it.
So you've got a good idea of what they're going to like with you.
What makes them go weak and what are their limits?
So when it comes to sort of punishments and rewards, like
you want to know what is going to make your sub feel punished and what is going to
make them feel rewarded. So yeah, asking them questions like this and also obviously
what are their limits? So you know what their boundaries are and you don't overstep
the boundaries, it's a good idea. And who's their perfect Dom and
what does she do to them? So yeah, you can really, you know, be quite blunt with
the questions you're asking so you can get as much information as possible that are
going to help you in your sessions. Is there anything you'd add to that, G?
I actually have a list of questions that I ask if
it's more of a full-time, you know, arrangements, if it's just someone who just came
on the cam quick, like straight away, a new one, I'm not going to sit there and ask
them 18 questions because it'll be a bit much, but if we've got a full thing going
on, then I'll tell them I have a list of questions I want you to answer and maybe
I'll even send them in the email so then he can do it in his own time and really
put effort into the answers because if it's a full-time arrangement, like Rell just
said, we really need to get to know them because if we know exactly what they want,
we can deliver that to them. If, of course, if we want, if that's within our boundaries
too. And then, yeah, if you know exactly what they want, then they're going to keep
coming back because you can give it to them and they're like, you know, yeah, anyway,
I'm just going off on one here, but I'll read out the questions.
I know there's quite a lot more and you're probably not going to remember them all,
but maybe you can watch this back and write them down.
This is what I ask my full-time subs. So yeah, I wrote, what do you enjoy most
about the Dom sub relationship? Describe your perfect Dom.
What makes you go completely weak? Regarding humiliation and insults, how harsh do
you like it? Are you into chastity? Are you into SPH, which is small penis
humiliation? Are you into sissification? Are you into cuckold?
Are you into cock and ball torture? Are you into anal play?
What are your limits? How much time do you have to devote to me?
What are your fantasies? Tell me something you've not told anybody else.
How do you plan to please me? What do you want from me?
What might I find you useful for? What services can you provide for me?
Do you have any specialised skills that may be of use to me?
And finally, is there anything else you would like to tell me?
So I just asked them that and then I feel like it just covers so much.
And then you'll get so much good like information from that that you can use in all
of your sessions. You'll know exactly what they want, exactly what they don't want.
You know, like you'll find out so much about them.
And then, yeah, and then you've just got, you know, all different things that you
can implement into your sessions. So yeah, that's what I like to do.
But like I said, not with the ones who just come into the chats because that will
definitely overwhelm them. But if it's a full-time arrangement, then it's totally
fine to ask them questions, especially when you're, you know, not in the session.
Like I wouldn't be doing, like I wouldn't be in a session with them, doing like dominating
them and then whip out all of these questions.
I would do it outside of the session, you know?
So yeah, I think that's it for that one, isn't it?
Yeah. Georgia, sorry guys, could I just add something?
I've actually had an email from one of the staffs.
He literally like described what he likes and also he's done a list where he says,
my likes and my dislikes. So he's like, he's into all these domination, but then
like Anthony, he said, I'm not into humiliation, I'm not into this.
So which was quite helpful for me in a way.
But then also I think with me, I find it easier because I actually, years ago I actually
worked in a dungeon and the approach that we used to have was you meet
one of them, you know, you go in. And then you talk about whether it's your safe
word, whether it's this, whether it's that, and he was eating every one of them.
He was like so different that sometimes you just think, but you would remember them
because they were so specific. You know, and I had a guy who, who, you know, and
it was one of the bits where you said what it was that set them off.
And I realised it was a generational thing, because they were all certain age, and
it was something that was done to them at school.
And there was a guy that I used to see, and I had to wear, like, they called it American
tan pantyhose, which is a certain type, but as long as it's sheer on top, you know,
it doesn't cover it. And all he needed was, you know, while I was, while I was punishing
him, he had to have, he had to feel my tights, because the teacher that he used to
like, you know, when she punished him, he actually came, you know, when he was a
teenager. And it was quite weird, like, what it set him off, while the other one
was being insulted, while I wore the same pants, you know, and I remember thinking,
wow, you know, it was quite, it was, so you realise, like, at some point, certain
age, it's like a generational thing. So it must have been, you know, what women used
to wear at school, and, you know, how they wear the skirts and all that.
And I thought, wow, that was like quite interesting, you know.
Yeah. Thank you for sharing that. That's really interesting.
No worries. I love that. And I love, I love hearing about in like sub stories,
and what gets them into it, like, it's so interesting, isn't it?
Do you know what, like, there was, I had, I also had babies, if
that makes sense. And, you know, they would wear like, grown up nappies type of thing.
And it was all this, you know, like a mummy thing where you're nice to them, and
you hug them and all this, and literally, it just sets them off.
You know, because it was obviously something from their childhood, but it turns out
it wasn't a mother, it was a nanny, you know, but it was this whole thing, you know,
where they were, where you looked after them, and you sort of like, you know, change
the nappies and put cream on and slathered them in it.
And then I also had a guy who loved having someone smoke while he was on his
knees and use his mouth as an ashtray. Yeah, I've done that recently as well.
Do you know, he was just like, and he was always looking for someone that smokes,
you know, and I was like, my God, I'll end up getting cancer by the time I'm finished
with you. He was like, it was quite intense with him all the time.
He was just like, literally, and all he asked throughout the session was just to
have a bit of water. Yeah, yeah, there are so
many. You reminded me about the adult babies, actually, on the types.
I meant to put that on there, said that one, didn't I?
But I forgot about that. Yeah, they call it American fan pantyhose, which means it's
your, I actually have a pair, I'll show you, and it's actually, which is still sheer
on top, so they get to see everything, but it's like, one second, I'll get them.
Also, and it's funny because, you know, you've got all these different nudes,
nude tights, which I used to think, is it the same, but now they're called the American
fan pantyhose, and it's a particular brand of nude.
And even though these are a tad bit shiny, they prefer if they went shiny, because
apparently that's where they used to wear it.
So you see, like, it's all clear. Yeah, yeah, they remind me of Jess, she likes to
wear those. Yeah, this is it, you know, and it's like, that's their thing, you know,
they're not worried about what you do and what the top is and whatever.
It's, that's the thing. Yeah, and the clothing, I mean, that's a big thing, isn't
it, as well? It is, yeah, that's like a big, big thing, what you wear and how you
wear it, as well. Yeah. Thank you so much for sharing.
Thank you. You're welcome. Is it Nat? Nat, yeah.
Hello, good to meet you. Nice to meet you.
Do you know what we actually met before? I started last year with you guys, but I
was, I had some time out, so. Okay, well, welcome back.
Thank you. Glad to be back. Amazing picture there from one
of our dungeon picks. I like that. Very good.
Okay, do you want to go through what to see and do?
Yeah, sure. Okay, so don't rush. Like
I said earlier, you know, sometimes like new doms may think that, you know, they've
got to have all the answers and make them do this and make them do that and blah,
blah, blah. Like, no, it doesn't need to be like that.
You can just take a breath, you know, relax and just, just go with the flow.
You don't need to rush it at all. Always remain in your
power with your attention out onto them. This is your session and you control how
it goes. So there might be moments in the session where you're like, oh, where do
I take this from here? I've already done all the things.
That I know that he likes or, you know, this or that.
So, but that's fine. Just always know that you're in control of it.
And even if you think, what do I do next?
You can tell him. For example, if you Google the sub poses, there's
like a big list of different poses that you can make them do.
So just an easy one, like a quick one that you'll always remember is get on your
knees below me. You can have him waist on his knees below you with his head down.
And you can just say, I just wanna see you down there for a moment or something like
that. And then you could even just like go onto our website, look at the domination
course and I'm sure there'd be something on there that would inspire you to, you
know, what you can do with them or just Google something or I don't know.
So yeah, so never feel like you have to try and come up with all these ideas
and you know, if you're running out of ideas, you can just make them do something
as simple as that, like get on your knees below me and then maybe something will
pop up in your head or maybe you can Google something.
So yeah, that's that one. Use actions and props.
So if they like small penis humiliation, you can do actions like this, you know,
like, or like this, like you're mimicking how small their penis is.
Sometimes they like the loser sign. You can do the whole loser.
And with props as well, I now have a strap-on that I actually just use as
a joke in one of my shows that I don't actually use on anybody yet, but I put that
strap-on on and show like, you know, show them the strap-on and like tell them what
I'm gonna do to them with it. And they absolutely love it.
I only just got this recently and I'm like, oh, I should have had this all this time.
So obviously with the props, you're not gonna actually use them on them because they're
on the other side of the screen, you know, but just having the prop, it just adds
something to it. And especially if you're wearing it or you're holding it, if it's
a whip or a gag or, you know, a leash or so many different props you could use.
And maybe some of you already have these things at home anyway, maybe even like handcuffs,
maybe a lot of people have them. Or if you don't have this stuff, even just household
items. So like a rolling pin or something like that, or a spatula, you can tell them
you're gonna, you know, stick the rolling pin up his arse or whip him with the spatula,
I don't know. So you can just like holding it and whipping your own hand, you know,
something like that. All of these things can help and it's something that just takes
up a little bit more time in your session.
And you can tell yourself- Sorry, can I just quickly, sorry, what you said about
the props. I mean, I still see, I still have like two of my clients that I have seen
for like 20, past 20 years. Now, one of them, his thing is about being
a slut, you know, dressing up as a woman and all this and being told, you know, so
I just tend to talk to him a lot, tell him I'm gonna take him out, I'm gonna get
all these people to do things to him and he won't be able to see because you wanna
be a proper slut and blah, blah, blah. And he's, what he hates is a carrot.
He hates carrots because he was made to eat them as a kid.
So whenever he wants something up his bottom, he's a carrot.
And it's just, I know, and it's so weird, you know, but as soon as I mentioned a
carrot, that's it, you know. He's like over the moon.
And this is what you said about using like certain props.
It's just about once you get to know what it is that they want, another one that
I've got, his thing is where I humiliate him and I tell him he cannot do anything.
And I usually tell him, because he says he's a piggy, he's my piggy bank.
So, and I tend to tell him, it's that financial humiliation.
And I usually, if he looks up and I usually tell him, no, no, no, no, tail up, which
is his thingy, obviously. And I always tell him, tail up, head down, no talk.
And he loves the fact that I'm like controlling everything.
And I tell him, and I usually tell him, I'm better than you and knowledge is power.
And I make him repeat it over and over again.
And that makes him cum. Wow. I know. It just shows, doesn't it, how different,
like- Everyone's so different, yeah. Yeah.
And this is why it's good to not assume and just, oh, I've got a sub, so you must,
you've got a small dick or, you know, something like that, because maybe they don't
like that. Or, you know, like you just, it's not good to assume that they're all
going to be into the same- That's when you ask them and you get to know them.
Because that's like a long-term thing, as you said, yeah.
So there's like a big difference between them.
Once you get to know them, you know what sets them off and what it is, and you just
keep teasing them. Exactly. Thank you for sharing.
I like the rolling pin thing. I didn't do that, I swear.
I've got one, I must use it. Yeah. But yeah, with the props, obviously,
you've got the props on your side that you can use, you know, and show them on your
side. But then also, of course, you can have them use stuff on themselves.
I actually, in the questions that I asked one of my subs in those 18 questions that
I asked, he said that he liked nipple clamps.
So then I had him go out and buy some nipple clamps.
And even if, like I said, even if they don't have the things there and then, you
can just have them use anything on themselves.
Eggs or anything. Anything. I had one get a toothbrush, stick it up himself,
and then brush his teeth. And he loved it.
He absolutely loved it. He wanted extremes.
Like nothing was extreme enough for this guy.
So I was like, right, go get your toothbrush.
So yeah, just be creative and look around your own room.
If like you're thinking about what to do with them, just look around your room and
then you might think, oh yeah, we can go get that hairbrush.
And you know, they can get a hairbrush and stick it up themselves or whatever.
I don't know. Or spank themselves. Something else that maybe I might've done.
Or get them to describe their room that they're in to you.
That's something that I've done that takes a bit of time as well.
Like describe your surroundings to me. Like, so I know, like, is there anything that
I can use or get him to use in some way? Yeah, amazing.
Okay. On that point, you said that you made someone buy nipple clamps.
It just reminded me that I had this sub in my room, didn't I, recently.
And he was like, oh, I've spoken to you. He said he'd spoken to Georgia before.
So I was like, oh, Georgia, I'm speaking to this guy.
He said that you just dumped him before. And she was like, yeah, tell him to go get
the nipple clamps. She meant that she made him buy.
So that was really good. So I did. Yeah, I know.
He was a good one. I had him for a long stint and then he faded away, but I will
get him back. You will get him back. Yeah, because they tend to come back.
They'll go around, but they always tend to come back.
Definitely. You can also tell your sub to call you mistress or whatever you like
and punish him when he doesn't. So when they're replying to you, you want them to
always say like, yes, mistress, or no mistress, or whatever it is.
And if they forget, then you can hand out punishments.
With the punishment, you can start off by gentle and then work your way up to
more severe ones. And that leads us on to using a safe word.
So it's good to always establish a safe word between yourself and your sub.
And also you can use traffic light words.
So, you know, when they're getting closer and closer to their limit.
This is a super important one and one that you should try not to forget because
it just, I think it just gives more reassurance to your
sub as well. One, that you fully know what you're doing because every single experienced
dom knows that it's really important to use a safe word.
And yeah, and it just keeps it obviously safer that you know that, you know, if it
is ever coming to their limit that they're gonna tell you.
And that they feel like they're able to tell you as well because if you didn't establish
a safe word, maybe they wouldn't think, oh, you know, I wanna tell her this because
you've not even allowed them to kind of thing.
So yeah, that's a little bit about what to do.
It needs to be about them, not necessarily just you.
Yeah, so they react to everything you say.
Yeah. The thing about doming is that you're holding a safe space for somebody else.
So it really is the other person, you know, you're offering a service to them.
It's them that are, you know, it's still about them, even though they're your sub,
it's still about them, yeah. So even though you're in control, ultimately the sub
is in control because they can stop it at any time with their safe word.
This is it, yeah. That's how it should be.
That's it, because unfortunately just one thing can like just pull them off because
it gets them out of that frame of mind. And another good reason to use a safe word
is that it gives them the freedom to say no.
If you have a safe word, then if they like to, as part of the play, which they might
do, they might like to say stop or no or whatever else.
And you know that it's so you don't have to stop because you've got a safe word.
They'll say the safe word if they really want it to stop.
So it means that they can kind of play with like saying no and stuff without having
to actually stop the play. Yeah, that's good, that's good.
Ooh, okay. Yeah, so a few just other
ideas. Gee's given loads already, but just a few extra things.
So spanking, self-spanking, you can get them to spank themselves.
Pain and reward, so sometimes people do like games where they'll
take so much pain, so many spanks or whatever it is to get a reward, whatever little
reward that might be, maybe the reward would be to worship you or something like
that. Ball busting, that's something probably you
do more of than I have. You can get them to do different things with their balls
basically, another way to inflict pain isn't it, or you can get them to tie up the
balls with a shoelace or something. Or
a stocking, I used to do the thing with a stocking.
Yeah, with a stocking that's a good idea.
I used to do that with a stocking and then you separate the balls, and I used to
say, oh that's your little package now, look.
And it's just about the way you do it, and it's quite good because you can tighten
it and then you can see their reaction as well, whether it's too much or whether
that's enough or if it's falling out obviously.
But as Hugo said, it's different when you're doing it on cam than if you're actually
doing it to them. Yeah, and you can get them to just, you can just get
them to pull them. I mean, you can just get them to pull them.
Or even number how much they're doing it, and stuff like that.
Worship, so obviously worship is a big part of the most kind of subs, isn't
it. You can get them to, like Gee said, get into a sub position and worship you,
show them how they'll worship you, worship your ass, your feet, whatever part of
your body that you like. Small penis humiliation, so we've talked about
that a little bit already. Controlled play, orgasm denial, so
like, I guess... To ask for permission. Yeah.
And yeah, just controlling the way that they play with themselves, if at all, if
they're allowed to touch themselves at all, and when.
Bringing them right up to, you know, edging, bringing them right up to orgasm and
then denying them and making them start again.
Games. Have you had, sorry girls, have you had, I'm sure you have, have you had anyone
with poppers on when they come up with poppers?
Yeah, because I've been getting that as well, yeah.
Yeah, quite often. Yeah, that is something that, you know, often comes along
with certain types of subs, doesn't it. Yeah, where it gives them that high, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. And they often like you to tell them to take it, you know.
Yeah, and how to take it and all that, yeah.
Which is obviously something just to be mindful about and to, you know, to look after
their wellbeing, obviously they're responsible.
Yeah, obviously, yeah. The first question should be are you on beta blockers?
Yeah, yeah, so something to be careful about there.
Yeah, games, so you can play, you can make up all different games.
I mean, you can have fun with it, can't you?
That's the thing as well about, you know, it doesn't have to be serious all the time.
Like, you can have fun, you can laugh at them, you know, sometimes they like to be
laughed at. So, you know, like, I remember G making people sing like, I'm a little
teapot and stuff like that. You can do stuff like that with
them or like, you can sometimes flip a coin and like, if it's heads, you've got to
do this, tails that, like. Right, right on themselves.
I am, I am still, I am still. Yeah, you can make them write
on themselves, you know, like, sluck with your chest or you just make them do different
things. I like to incorporate like, flip of a coin or a card or something just to
make it a bit more fun and drag it out a little bit.
And making them perform for you, like I said, you know, making them sing a song or
recite something or twerk. Whatever it is that you can make them
do, that will be fun and humiliating for them if that's what they're into.
Anything else on that, Julie? I think we've covered a lot there.
I'm trying to think if we've got any more ideas.
Well, yeah, I think that's it for now. Yeah.
Okay, oh, outfit inspiration. So just a few pics from the shoot.
Like Nat said, like, what you wear is quite important, so.
Latex tends to be a hit, doesn't it? Leather, chains, you know, if you look the
part, then you'll also feel the part, which makes you feel better as well, doesn't
it, in session. It does, yeah. Makes you feel powerful.
And it doesn't have to cost loads of money.
Like there are some, there's some good stuff on sheen or whatever, you know, that
you can get for quite cheap PVC stuff. Or there's the latex lady
that we work with. If you're ever interested in getting like bespoke latex made,
she's really reasonable. She's quite really, really good for what she makes.
And she's amazing. That red thing that Sammy's wearing there is one of my pieces
from her. She's awesome. Yeah, it's lovely, isn't it?
Yeah, so thinking about your outfit and in that as well, obviously there's what you're
wearing, but like where you are, like your setting as well, you know, you can think
about your setting, like maybe, like G said with props, maybe you might have some
laid out behind you or, you know, depending on what mood you're going for, you might
be in different areas of the house or, you know, with different things in your background.
Yeah, and also obviously, you know, you're considering what you're wearing, but then
we had a picture of T in his outfit there.
You can also consider what your sub is going to wear.
So if it's a sissy or something like that, then obviously they're going to be wearing
women's clothing and usually in session, the naked as well, because a
lot of them like the fantasy of the whole clothed female, naked male.
But then that doesn't mean that you can't have them wear an outfit and then strip.
You can have them do a sexy strip and like strip out of it for you.
You can have them like, you know, that can take some time up as well.
So yeah, you can have them go out and buy some things for themselves.
And if you've got a really great sub, they can buy outfits for their mistress, which
is amazing. So you can have them like, you know, go and buy you something.
You can tell them exactly what you want, or you can tell them, you know, go and buy
me an outfit that you want to see your mistress in, you know, make sure that it's
a nice one, blah, blah, blah. So yeah, you can have them buy them for you.
And also with the outfit, a lot of subs, like if they're into the whole
latex fetish, they like to hear the sound of the latex.
So you can put your camera, your sound on and just rub like your latex and
it makes a noise. Like, you know, cause it's like a plasticky material.
It makes a specific noise. So yeah, you can do that.
And some of them will love it. Like if they like it, then they like that thing.
They absolutely go wild to hear the sound of your latex.
So that's something else to consider if you're wearing latex.
So yes, that's that. And a good question to ask the questions like, have you got
any fetishes? Because, you know, latex can be a fetish, rubber can be a fetish.
Like it's good to know if they have any fetishes.
Definitely. That was good. Yeah. And so we're onto the
last bit. So remember, although there are different types of subs
and categories of kinks, every individual is different.
So it's okay. And a good thing, if you don't know exactly what they want straight
away. Some cam sessions might be short and sweet.
Sometimes a proper sub-dom relationship takes time to develop.
And as you develop your inner dom, you can experiment with what you enjoy.
So most subs love to please their mistress and genuinely enjoying sessions will bring
you loyal clients. So yeah, I mean, we talked a lot there about what the
client wants, what they might like, what they might want to do, but ultimately, you
know, you shouldn't be doing anything that you don't want to do.
And it's your pleasure. So just experimenting and finding out what it is you
find fun or enjoyable and, you know, doing more of that, you know, communicating
with your subs as well, that this is what you like and this is what you enjoy.
So it's about finding your own, your yourself in it as well, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. Any questions? Does anyone have any
questions or just anything they want to add?
If anyone wants to add anything else, I know we've got some people with some experience
in here. Anybody have any questions or anything?
I'm trying to see all the cams. No. Okay.
Anything anybody wants to add? Anything else you want to add?
Yeah, you see, like for me, you know, like exactly what you said about what you enjoy
and what you don't enjoy. You know, sometimes I used to get people and I used to
think, oh, really? But once I start, I get so much into it.
And I think they can tell you enjoy, you know, what you're doing, and they tend to
come back. And it's just really, I sometimes surprise myself and I think, how the
hell did I come up with that? But I think once you're in that frame of mind, you
just sort of like go, you know? And it's, I think it's quite good, but as you both
said, you enjoy it. You know, it's very important to ask what it is and then you
take everything from it and then you just work along it.
And then you get used to what they like and what they don't like, but they will notice
if you enjoy it or you don't, you know? And as you said, I think if you force yourself,
they can tell, you know? Yeah. And it's good to, and it's also good to note that
not every, I know we say this in all our training with all types of, like, clients,
but not every sub will be for every dom. Exactly.
You either click or you don't. You can't deal with them.
Yeah. And that's fine. That's fine. That doesn't mean anything about you or it's
not, nothing. Exactly. It doesn't, like, it works both ways, you know?
You either click or you don't, you know? Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. So just don't beat yourself up if you're not clicking.
Yeah, that's it. Fine. Okay, ladies, I think that brings us to the end
then for today. Thank you so much. Thank you.
We'll put the recording up on the website in the members area.
So if you wanted to watch any of it back or for anybody that wants to catch up with
it, they can do. Perfect. Thank you so much for coming and thank you for your input
for all your input as well. Thank you. We'll see you soon, hopefully.
See you soon. Take care. Bye, everyone. Thank you for coming.
Thank you.